Got a brioche bun here.
先来俩奶油面包
And get that toasted really quick.
快速拿火烤一下
Doesn't that look pleasant?
看上去真耐人
I want to keep it mostly soft but slightly crispy in the middle.
想让面包基本松软，但中间稍微脆些
And on the bottom, I'm going to go with the base of this Beer'n Brat Mustard.
底下嘛，我要抹上这种芥末酱
And of course, some duke's mayo on top.
当然，上面抹的是蛋黄酱
Some romaine.
再来些莴苣叶
Let's get it all crunched up.
把叶子掰碎
A rather pleasant little tomato here from... a place that grows them.
还有这个耐人的小西红柿，来自……生长它的地方:-\
Some ground black peppercorn.
磨些黑胡椒
Some ground pink Himalayan Salt.
再磨些盐
Lovely little cucumber, heck yeah, cucumbers.
还有这小黄瓜
It's that time of year, I don't know, I'm in the mood~
一年没吃了，怎么说呢，我就想吃
Not looking for a whole bunch, just... yeah.
不要整个，这些就够了
Just a taste of it.
就为了这脆劲
Going to go with a little spritz of basil, not much.
再来一小撮香叶，不要太多
Man, I got some turkey, some Mesquite wood smoked.
还有这用牧豆树熏制的火鸡肉
And lastly, got some pepper jack cheese with little bits of jalapeno in there.
最后，来点辣芝士，里面有墨西哥胡椒
That'll do.
这就行
Ah man, this stuff melts beautifully.
好的，烤制的样子不错
There we go.
就这样
Haha, look at that, I know we don't need to cut it in half, but i feel like seeing it.
再看看，我知道这玩意没必要切成两半，但看上去好啊
And there looks like taste. Mm~
看上去就直流口水了(瞧把您馋的)
Yeah, for chips we got a dirty classic original recipe, sour cream and onion.
这期的薯片呢，是酸奶油洋葱味的
Oh yeah, and smell that already.
好家伙，味道这就窜出来了
And naturally we gotta give it for some pickles here.
自然地，我们还需要放腌菜
Well, I'm going with some pickled okra.
不过这回，我要放腌秋葵
Oh, these are big'ol okra pieces, good grief.
天哪，咋这么大块啊
Yeah, just a couple of those will do.
放两块差不多了
I cannot stop eating these lately, this is gonna be good.
我要赶紧吃掉，绝对很香的
[Applause]
注 入 灵 魂
Oh man, I haven't eaten a sandwich in like a year.
天哪，我有一年没吃三明治了
Actually not true, [chuckle] but it has been a while, hasn't?
实际上并不是，但是也有好久了
Let's try this thing.
赶紧尝尝吧
Immediately that mesquite turkey is just going right through everything else,
显然熏制火鸡的味道扩散了整个三明治
coming out on top, even though it's in the middle.
直至三明治上面，尽管它是放在了中间
Honestly, I could have gone for, maybe just a little more of the tomato. Just a little bit.
说真的，再放些火柿子会更好，再放一些就好
And then having that hint of cucumber, I don't know, not everyone likes cukes.
然后是黄瓜的感觉，不知为何，有些人不喜欢黄瓜
I rather enjoy them for a summery feel, in the... summer.
我还很喜欢它所蕴含的夏天的感觉
Actually, it's like another piece of cucumber. Slightly thicker (than) tomato.
实际上，嘴里的是块黄瓜吧，比火柿子硬些
That's about all that would change about this, because this is an awesome combo.
口感的变化就说到这，这搭配简直完美
Yeah, right there.
没错，就这样
That kind of just bite all the way through, magnificent.
一口下去，多重享受，无与伦比
Actually, made the exact same thing just with burger instead of turkey
说真的，今天国庆给自己做火鸡肉三明治
for my own fourth of July things. And uh... yeah, it was awesome.
而不是普通汉堡，真挺好的
And I like cucumbers were pickles, but you know.
当然，我还是喜欢腌黄瓜的，不过想换换口味了
All right, chip time.
好的，尝尝薯片
Can't go wrong, sour cream and onion.
酸奶油洋葱味，不会错的
I really like the, uh, Dirty Chips.
挺喜欢这个Dirty(脏的)牌薯片的
Contrary to the name, they're not actually terribly dirty.
不像牌子表面说的那样，他们做的东西不差
And they're just, kind of lightly seasoned with
他们就用这种味道的调料
whatever it's supposed to taste like, sour cream and onion.
给薯片调味，这种酸奶油洋葱味的
It's particularly light.
薯片很轻的
Okay, it's time for this...[laugh] ridiculous okra.
好的，现在我要尝尝这……大得离谱的秋葵
Why is he so long?
咋就这么长～呢？
Very mildly spicy. I guess I did pick up the... mildly spicy one,
有一点辣，估计我拿的就是微辣的吧
But that's what it is. I like it.
不过本来就是这样，我很喜欢
And I know, obviously i still love pickles, but pickled everything?
当然，我还是很喜欢腌黄瓜的，不过其他的腌制食品就另说了
I've just been doing pickled everything over the past.
我一直都在腌制东西吃
I don't even know how long.
我都不知道啥时候开始腌东西吃
Yeah, if I can pickle it and it's a vegetable-like thing,
如果这是蔬菜啥的，并且被腌过的话
then i will probably eat it. Anyway... [chuckle]
我大概就吃了，无论如何……
Well, I hope you're hungry now, because I am.
希望大家饿了，因为我饿了
See you in about a year.
一年后见:-\
I'm just kidding. I'll try to do more of these
开个玩笑啦，以后还会有更多的:-)